<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SecureWifi</string>
    <string name="get_wifi_scan_results">Scan access points nearby</string>
    <string name="connect_to_wifi">Connect to Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="starting_scan">Starting scanning…</string>
    <string name="attempting_to_connect">Connecting to %1$s (%2$d/%3$d) \nPassword: %4$s (%5$d/%6$d) \nSpeed: %7$d passwords/min \n</string>
    <string name="password_hacking_results">Password was hacked!\nNetwork: %1$s \nPassword: %2$s\nPassword was guessed in %3$d attempts</string>
    <string name="couldnt_find_password">No vulnerabilities in Wi-Fi points were found in a quick scan.</string>
    <string name="disconnect_from_wifi">Disconnect from Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="check_password_security">Check the security of passwords of nearby networks</string>
    <string name="list_of_wifi_nearby">Wi-Fi nearby</string>
    <string name="check_of_passwords_safety">Check</string>
    <string name="security_check_results">Results</string>
    <string name="connection_start_failure">An error occurred when trying to start connection attempts. Please try again later</string>
    <string name="scan_failure">An error occurred during the scan. Please try again later</string>
    <string name="performing_connections">Attempting to connect to networks nearby</string>
    <string name="connection_attempts_ended_success">Password was hacked!</string>
    <string name="connection_attempts_ended_nothing_found">The check is completed</string>
    <string name="attempting_to_connect_notification">Wifi: %1$s (%2$d/%3$d) \nPassword: %4$s (%5$d/%6$d)</string>
    <string name="password_hacking_results_notification">Network: %1$s \nPassword: %2$s</string>
    <string name="couldnt_find_password_notification">No vulnerabilities in Wi-Fi points were found.</string>
    <string name="signal_level">%1$d/10</string>
    <string name="passwords_checked">Passwords checked:</string>
    <string name="password_was_hacked">Password was hacked</string>
    <string name="password_was_not_hacked">Password was not hacked</string>
    <string name="signal">Signal level:</string>
    <string name="wifi_signal_level">Wifi signal level</string>
    <string name="new_password_hint">Add password…</string>
    <string name="add_button">Add button</string>
    <string name="password_delete_imageview">Password delete imageview</string>
    <string name="attack_wifi">Attack point</string>
    <string name="password_list">Password list:</string>
    <string name="see_wifi_attack_results">See wifi security check results</string>
    <string name="tried_passwords">List of tried passwords:</string>
    <string name="custom_lists">Custom lists</string>
    <string name="password_list_delete_imageview">Password list delete imageview\n</string>
    <string name="add_new_custom_password_list">Add new custom password list</string>
    <string name="edit_custom_list">Editing of the list</string>
    <string name="adaptive">Adaptive</string>
    <string name="most_popular">Most popular</string>
    <string name="list_name_hint">List name</string>
    <string name="save_list_name">Save list</string>
    <string name="enter_list_name">Enter list name</string>
    <string name="list_name_already_exist">List with this name already exists</string>
    <string name="plus_adaptive_passwords">+ Adaptive passwords</string>
    <string name="wifi_attack_results">Wifi attack results</string>
    <string name="correct_password_is">Point password: %1$s</string>
    <string name="menu_refresh">Scan Wi-Fi again</string>
    <string name="select_all">Select all</string>
    <string name="deselect_all">Deselect all</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="no_results_yet">There are no results yet</string>
    <string name="no_password_lists_selected">-No password lists selected-</string>
    <string name="something_and_n_others">%1$s and %2$d others</string>
    <string name="no_wifies_selected">-No Wi-Fi points selected-</string>
    <string name="passwords_amt">Passwords: %d</string>
    <string name="total_passwords_amt">Passwords: %d</string>
    <string name="wifi_info">Wi-Fi info</string>
    <string name="wpa_short_explanation">Support of Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA) security</string>
    <string name="wpa2_short_explanation">Support of Wi-Fi Protected Access II (WPA2) security</string>
    <string name="wep_short_explanation">Support of Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP) security</string>
    <string name="ess_short_explanation">Network is a part of Extended Service Set (ESS) configuration</string>
    <string name="ibss_short_explanation">Network is a part of Ad Hoc (or Independent Basic Service Set (IBSS) or Peer-to-Peer) configuration</string>
    <string name="wps_short_explanation">Support of WPS (Wi-Fi Protected Setup) mechanism</string>
    <string name="rsn_short_explanation">Support of RSN (Robust Security Network)</string>
    <string name="psk_short_explanation">Network uses Pre-Shared Key (PSK) authentication</string>
    <string name="eap_short_explanation">Network uses Extensible Authentication Protocol (EAP) authentication</string>
    <string name="tkip_short_explanation">Network uses Temporal Key Integrity Protocol (TKIP) encryption</string>
    <string name="ccmp_short_explanation">Network uses Counter Mode with Cipher Block Chaining Message Authentication Code Protocol (CCMP) encryption, a.k.a. AES-CCMP</string>
    <string name="open_short_explanation">Network is open and does not require authentication or encryption</string>
    <string name="ieee8021x_short_explanation">Network uses IEEE 802.1X authentication</string>
    <string name="passpoint_short_explanation">It is a Passpoint Network</string>
    <string name="wpa_explanation">Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA) — security certification program that became available in 2003. The Wi-Fi Alliance intended it as an intermediate measure in anticipation of the availability of the more secure and complex WPA2. The WPA protocol implements the Temporal Key Integrity Protocol (TKIP). WPA also includes a Message Integrity Check. Researchers have since discovered a flaw in WPA that relied on older weaknesses in WEP and the limitations of the message integrity code hash function, named Michael, to retrieve the keystream from short packets to use for re-injection and spoofing.</string>
    <string name="wpa2_explanation">Ratified in 2004, WPA2 replaced WPA. WPA2, which requires testing and certification by the Wi-Fi Alliance, implements the mandatory elements of IEEE 802.11i. In particular, it includes support for CCMP, an AES-based encryption mode. In particular, it includes support for CCMP, an AES-based encryption mode. Certification began in September, 2004. From March 13, 2006, to June 30, 2020, WPA2 certification was mandatory for all new devices to bear the Wi-Fi trademark. In WPA2-protected WLANs, secure communication is established through a multi-step process. Initially, devices associate with the Access Point (AP) via an association request. This is followed by a 4-way handshake, a crucial step ensuring both the client and AP have the correct Pre-Shared Key (PSK) without actually transmitting it. During this handshake, a Pairwise Transient Key (PTK) is generated for secure data exchange.</string>
    <string name="wep_explanation">WEP encrypts traffic using a 64- or 128-bit key in hexadecimal. This is a static key, which means all traffic, regardless of device, is encrypted using a single key. A WEP key allows computers on a network to exchange encoded messages while hiding the messages\' contents from intruders. This key is what is used to connect to a wireless-security-enabled network. One of WEP’s main goals was to prevent Man-in-the-Middle attacks, which it did for a time. However, despite revisions to the protocol and increased key size, various security flaws were discovered in the WEP standard over time. As computing power increased, it became easier to exploit for criminals to exploit those flaws. Because of its vulnerabilities, the Wi-Fi Alliance officially retired WEP in 2004.</string>
    <string name="ess_explanation">An extended service set (ESS) is a wireless network, created by multiple access points, which appears to users as a single, seamless network, such as a network covering a home or office that is too large for reliable coverage by a single access point. It is a set of one or more infrastructure basic service sets on a common logical network segment (i.e. same IP subnet and VLAN). Extended service sets make possible distribution services such as centralized authentication.</string>
    <string name="ibss_explanation">Independent Basic Service Set (IBSS), as the name suggests, is a service set that allows wireless devices or stations to communicate with each other without any medium or central device. It does not contain or include any AP (Access Point). That’s why it is also known as an ad hoc mode or peer to peer network. Peer to peer network, simply means two to more devices or stations or PCs connected to each other directly and share resources without any separate server computer. IBSS is a service set that is rarely used. It is only required when two to more devices such as mobile, laptops, tablets, etc. want to share or transfer files without connecting to any wireless network that an AP provides.</string>
    <string name="wps_explanation">Wi-Fi Protected Setup (WPS) (originally, Wi-Fi Simple Config) is a network security standard to create a secure wireless home network. Created by Cisco and introduced in 2006, the point of the protocol is to allow home users who know little of wireless security and may be intimidated by the available security options to set up Wi-Fi Protected Access, as well as making it easy to add new devices to an existing network without entering long passphrases. It is used by devices made by HP, Brother and Canon for their printers. WPS is a wireless method that is used to connect certain Wi-Fi devices such as printers and security cameras to the Wi-Fi network without using any password. n addition, there is another way to connect called WPS Pin that is used by some devices to connect to the wireless network. \nA major security flaw was revealed in December 2011 that affects wireless routers with the WPS PIN feature, which most recent models have enabled by default. The flaw allows a remote attacker to recover the WPS PIN in a few hours with a brute-force attack and, with the WPS PIN, the network\'s WPA/WPA2 pre-shared key (PSK).</string>
    <string name="rsn_explanation">The term Robust Security Network is used in WiFi networks to describe the security enhancements encompassed in the IEEE 802.11i and WPA (WiFi Protected Access) 1 and 2 variants. The suite of protocols endeavours to compensate for the weaknesses associated with WEP (Wired Equivalent Privacy). More specifically, RSN dynamically negotiates the authentication and encryption algorithms to be used for communications between WAPs and wireless clients. This means that as new threats are discovered, new algorithms can be added.</string>
    <string name="psk_explanation">Pre-Shared Key (PSK) is a security mechanism used in WPA to establish a secure connection between a wireless client and a Wi-Fi access point. When using WPA with PSK, a shared secret key is configured on both the access point and the client devices. This key is used to encrypt and decrypt the data exchanged between the client and the access point. The PSK is typically a passphrase or password that is known to both the network administrator (who configures the access point) and the users of the network (who enter the passphrase on their devices). WPA2 and WPA3 also support PSK.</string>
    <string name="eap_explanation">Extensible Authentication Protocol (EAP) is an authentication framework for providing the transport and usage of material and parameters generated by EAP methods. EAP methods are some common functions and negotiation of authentication methods that EAP provides. There are currently about 40 different methods defined. EAP is in wide use. For example, in IEEE 802.11 (Wi-Fi) the WPA and WPA2 standards have adopted IEEE 802.1X (with various EAP types) as the canonical authentication mechanism.</string>
    <string name="tkip_explanation">Temporal Key Integrity Protocol (TKIP) is a security protocol used in the IEEE 802.11 wireless networking standard. TKIP was designed as an interim solution to replace WEP without requiring the replacement of legacy hardware. This was necessary because the breaking of WEP had left Wi-Fi networks without viable link-layer security, and a solution was required for already deployed hardware. However, TKIP itself is no longer considered secure, and was deprecated in the 2012 revision of the 802.11 standard. TKIP uses the same underlying mechanism as WEP, and consequently is vulnerable to a number of similar attacks, such as packet spoofing and decryption, Royal Holloway attack and NOMORE attack.</string>
    <string name="ccmp_explanation">CCMP is the standard encryption protocol for use with the Wi-Fi Protected Access II (WPA2) standard and is much more secure than the Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP) protocol and Temporal Key Integrity Protocol (TKIP) of Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA). Because CCMP is a block cipher mode using a 128-bit key, it is secure against attacks to the 264 steps of operation. Generic meet-in-the-middle attacks do exist and can be used to limit the theoretical strength of the key to 2^n/2 (where n is the number of bits in the key) operations needed.</string>
    <string name="open_explanation">Using public Wi-Fi networks means exposure to numerous security pitfalls. Main three of them are Man-in-the-Middle (MitM) Attacks, Rogue Wi-Fi Networks (Wi-Fi networks set up by hackers that mimic legitimate ones but are actually designed to capture data), Malware Insertion. Any data transmitted over a public Wi-Fi session is at risk of being intercepted.</string>
    <string name="ieee8021x_explanation">IEEE 802.1X is an IEEE Standard for port-based network access control (PNAC). It is part of the IEEE 802.1 group of networking protocols. It provides an authentication mechanism to devices wishing to attach to a LAN or WLAN. The standard directly addresses a type of hacking called "DarkVishnya". However, there are some serious vulnerabilities found in 802.1X-2001 and 802.1X-2004 specifications, including a man in the middle attack, MAC spoofing and EAPOL-Logoff attacks.</string>
    <string name="passpoint_explanation">In a Passpoint network, devices are authenticated automatically, reducing the need for manual logins while ensuring only authorized users gain access. This feature is particularly beneficial in environments where quick, secure connectivity is essential, such as in retail or hospitality sectors. Passpoint uses enterprise security with the latest security protocols, such as WPA2 and WPA3,for enhanced security and protection against hacking attempts.</string>
</resources>